

SÉRGIO GARRIDO

PROGRAMADOR

CONTACTOS

926858480

✓ SGARRIDO.PRO@GMAIL.COM

GITHUB.COM/GARRIDO02

in SÉRGIOGARRIDO

SKILLS EM PROGRAMAÇÃO



€ JAVA

.js JAVASCRIPT

✓> FULL STACK

SQL

PERFIL

Utilizando a minha experiência internacional em gestão, liderança e formação de equipas tenho como objetivo pessoal e profissional transmitir e aplicar o máximo dos meus conhecimentos, de modo a conseguir atingir eficazmente quaisquer objetivos propostos.

EXPERIÊNCIA

AUXILIAR DE INVESTIGAÇÃO - PROJECTO 'GLÓRIA' NOVA SCHOOL OF SCIENCE & TECHNOLOGY | 2023 - PRESENTE

FORMADOR INTERNACIONAL
HOLMES PLACE ACADEMY | JUNHO 2020 - PRESENTE

FITNESS TRAINER & GROUP MANAGER HOLMES PLACE | AGOSTO 2019 - PRESENTE

EDUCAÇÃO

COMPUTER & SOFTWARE ENGINEERING
NOVA SCHOOL OF SCIENCE & TECHNOLOGY | 2023 - PRESENTE

CS50'S - WEB PROGRAMMING WITH PYTHON & JAVASCRIPT HARVARD UNIVERSITY | 2023

CS50'S - INTRODUCTION TO COMPUTER SCIENCE HARVARD UNIVERSITY | 2023

MESTRADO EM TREINO DE ALTO RENDIMENTO FACULDADE DE MOTRICIDADE HUMANA | 2021 - 2023

CCP - FORMAÇÃO PEDAGÓGICA DE FORMADORES HOLMES PLACE ACADEMY | 2021

CIÊNCIAS DO DESPORTO - MENOR EM EXERCÍCIO E SAÚDE FACULDADE DE MOTRICIDADE HUMANA | 2016 - 2019

COMPETÊNCIAS PESSOAIS

- Capacidade de integrar, formar e gerir equipas a nível Europeu
- Planeamento e desenvolvimento de projetos científicos
- Pensamento critico e inovador adaptado à atualidade
- Bom comunicador e motivador
- Fluente em Português e Inglês

PROJETOS

- Plataforma de Explicações Online
- Projeto Científico Pioneiro em Treino em Altitude
- Projeto Científico de LLM AI WebScrapping
- Fitness WebApp
- Social Network WebApp
- E-mail WebApp
- Stock Market Shares Webapp



SÉRGIO GARRIDO

PROGRAMMER

CONTACTOS

926858480

✓ SGARRIDO.PRO@GMAIL.COM

GITHUB.COM/GARRIDO02

in SÉRGIOGARRIDO

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

PYTHON

€ JAVA

.js JAVASCRIPT

✓> FULL STACK

SQL

PROFILE

Utilizing my international experience in team management, leadership and development my main personal and professional objetive is to pass on and apply the most of my knowledge in order to efficiently accomplish any established goals.

EXPERIENCE

RESEARCH ASSISTANT - PROJECT 'GLÓRIA' NOVA SCHOOL OF SCIENCE & TECHNOLOGY | 2023 - PRESENT

INTERNATIONAL LECTURER
HOLMES PLACE ACADEMY | JUNHO 2020 - PRESENT

FITNESS TRAINER & GROUP MANAGER HOLMES PLACE | AGOSTO 2019 - PRESENT

EDUCATION

COMPUTER & SOFTWARE ENGINEERING
NOVA SCHOOL OF SCIENCE & TECHNOLOGY | 2023 - PRESENTE

CS50'S - WEB PROGRAMMING WITH PYTHON & JAVASCRIPT HARVARD UNIVERSITY | 2023

CS50'S - INTRODUCTION TO COMPUTER SCIENCE HARVARD UNIVERSITY | 2023

MASTERS IN HIGH PERFORMANCE TRAININING FACULTY OF HUMAN KINETICS | 2021 - 2023

CCP - INSTRUCTOR COURSE
HOLMES PLACE ACADEMY | 2021

SPORTS SCIENCE - MINOR IN HEALTH AND EXERCISE FACULTY OF HUMAN KINETICS | 2016 - 2019

SOCIAL SKILLS

- Capacity to incorporate, develop and manage teams across Europe
- Planning & development of scientific projects
- Critical & innovative thinking
- Motivational speaker
- Fluent in English and Portuguese

PROJECTS

- Online Teaching Courses Platform
- LLM AI Scientific Project Webscrapping
- Pioneer Altitude Training Scientific Project
- Fitness WebApp
- Social Network WebApp
- E-mail WebApp
- Stock Market Shares Webapp